Eric Dickerson

Cocoa, Florida, United States



ericdickersonfree@gmail.com



+1 (321) 252 8922



linkedin.com/in/eric-dickerson102

Summary

- Always Open to Remote Job -

An experienced full-stack developer with 6 years of experience specializing in distributed systems and web3

technologies.

Launched several Ethereum and Solana Contracts, created NFTs and provided MVPs.

Following the client's business idea, I 've completed more than 10 projects related to various technical fields

from scratch.

I enjoy solving difficult technologies and I am good at creating technical solutions related to business use cases.

I value honor, integrity, punctuality and teamwork

Passionate about building world class web applications

Experience



OBLOCKCHAIN | FULL- STACK DEVELOPER

Omni X Labs

May 2022 - Oct 2022 (6 months)

- Developed the Omni X that provides tools for creating omnichain collections, bridging regular NFTs to ONFTs and cross-chain NFT sales.
- build a CI/CD pipeline with GitHub Actions
- Implemented the UI/UX design using Next, Typescript and Tailwind
- NFT Marketplace Backend Development using the Node.js, Express.js ,Moralis/Alchemy API, s3 bucket, AWS and MongoDB
- Test the node backend server by using the Jest / Mocha
- Tracked and fixed bugs and issues using GitHub as an issue tracking board

UD BLOCKCHAIN | FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Upwork

Oct 2019 - Apr 2022 (2 years 7 months)

- -Created the NFT minting website / Staking platform / Raffle platform/ Betting platform with Solidity and Rust on Solana and Ethereum network
- build the blockchain using the Golang and implement a basic, backend-based, custom blockchain application in Rust using Substrate
- write operation systems or microcontroller applications using the rust

- -web scraping tool with python, Machine learning tools, website with React.js&Node.js, Java project, Django/Flask server developemnt
- Android/IOS development with Flutter, React Native and Xamarin
- Presale / ICO / IDO / IGO / STO Development

BLOCKCHAIN | FULL- STACK DEVELOPER

MagicCraft Ltd.

Jan 2021 - Sep 2021 (9 months)

- -Created the ERC20 Token for Game Platform
- -Developed an ERC721 token contract as well as smart contract for democratic voting by token holders
- -Created the NFT Minting and Marketplace website with React/Redux and web3.js
- -Demonstrated wallet generation, ether and token transfers, balance ,checks, and listening for events
- -Advised on best security practices
- -Built a backend server for monitoring Binance contracts and creating transactions
- -Discord Bot for Marketing
- -Optimized the smart contract code and increased the efficiency by 15%, using the Library functionalities of the solidity

Full-stack Developer

Mazama

May 2019 - Dec 2020 (1 year 8 months)

- -Created the AI Chat bot for Facebook messenger
- -Interface development with Html, CSS, JavaScript, React, Typescript
- -Backend development with Django , Django Restful framework
- -NLP and NLU for AI using the Rasa

踵 Full-stack Developer

Kisko Products

Mar 2018 - Jan 2019 (11 months)

Developed a sports polling website (betpolls.com) that provides users with the betting odds on each game and a user-friendly voting system, and supports fantasy sports games.

Developed a back-end API using PHP, Lumen, and MySQL.

Created a web admin portal with React, Redux, and Shopify Polaris and a front-end portal with Laravel Blade templates and Bootstrap.

Implemented various search engine optimization techniques using Google Tag Manager and Ahrefs as SEO tools.

Education



National University of Singapore

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering Apr 2013 - Sep 2017

Skills

Rust (Programming Language) • Node.js • React.js • React Native • NoSQL • Python (Programming Language) • Django • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Solidity • web3.js